University and College Labor Education Association (UCLEA) Selected Files 6238
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
University and College Labor Education Association (UCLEA) Selected Files
1973- 2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
University and College Labor Education Association (UCLEA)
6238
4 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records.
6179181
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 11, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
University and College Labor Education Association
6179181
- NUEA Labor Education Committee 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NUEA board of Director Minutes 1979, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NUEA Minutes 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NUEA Board of Director Minutes 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NUCEA Minutes 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NUCEA Minutes 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NUEA Correspondence 1973-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NUCEA Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NUEA Regions 2, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NUEA Continuing Education Recruiter 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NUEA Pamphlets 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NUCEA Directories 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- NUCEA Correspondence 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- NUEA Forms (Box 1, Folder 14)
- NUCEA Forms (Box 1, Folder 15)
- NUCEA Pamphlets 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- NUCEA Newsletter 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- NUCEA Directories 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- UCLEA Correspondence 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- UCLEA Labor Studies Forum 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- UCLEA/WEL Local 189 Merger 2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Committee on Salary and Benefits Final Report 1977-1992 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Constitution, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Membership Directories 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Resource Directories, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Evaluation Summary Report 1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- UCLEA Executive Board Minutes 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Annual Meeting 1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Annual Meeting 1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Annual Meeting 1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Annual Meeting 1989 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Training Materials (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Labor Education/ Industrial Relations Nexus 1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- On the Triple Threat Professor (Box 1, Folder 48)
- To Strive for Excellence 1985 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Government Spending and the Economy 1986 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Education Update 1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Labor - Oriented Adult Degree Programs (Box 1, Folder 52)
- An Analysis of the Distribution of National/International Programs (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Fulbright Scholar Program 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- The Scales of Justice (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Labor Studies Journal Paper Guidelines, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Labor Studies Journal Transfer on Copyright Form (Box 2, Folder 2)
- UCLEA Call for Papers 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Unions and the Global Economy [Folder 1 of 2] 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Unions and the Global Economy [folder 2 of 2] 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- UCLEA Conference Papers [Folder 1 of 3] 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- UCLEA Conference Papers [folder 2 of 3] 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- UCLEA Conference Papers [Folder 3 of 3] 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO/UCLEA Joint Conference 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- UCLEA Call for Papers 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- UCLEA Evaluations 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- UCLEA Agenda 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- UCLEA Conference Packets 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Organizing for Keeps: Labor Studies Journal Papers 1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Labor Studies Journal Proofs Sent to Transaction 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- UCLEA Professional Council Survey 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- UCLEA Final Abstracts and Agenda 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- UCLEA Paper Presenters and Chairs 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO/UCLEA Conference Packet 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- UCLEA Call for Papers 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- UCLEA Paper Abstracts 1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- UCLEA Conference Changes 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- UCLEA Conference Papers [Folder 1 of 3] 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- UCLEA Conference Papers [Folder 2 of 3] 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- UCLEA Conference Papers [Folder 3 of 3] 1998 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- UCLEA Conference Comments 1998 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- UCLEA Evaluations 1998 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- UCLEA Evaluations 2000 (Box 2, Folder 28)